hello I'm swastika Bara and I'm really
excited to share that I have been
offered a role as a management traine at
ICI Lombard my journey pursuing pgdm in
marketing operations at bibm has
equipped me with strong skill sets and
deep industry knowledge my first step
into the corporate was through winter
internship program at ITC Kolkata and
summer internship program at barza
lifestyle which helped me to understand
the challenges in the corporate world
courses such as CRM sales and
distribution and consumer Behavior has
taught me how to identify the customer
needs and build effective engagement
strategies which help me to start my new
Journey at ICI lumbal
[Music]